英文字幕: Horriblesubs
中文字幕: 布尔
本字幕参照英文字幕和SweetSub字幕制作
可能会由于
1. 日译英的瑕疵
2. 英译汉的瑕疵
而产生偏差
请根据自己情况使用
或者等待更精确的版本
Use it at your own risk
我想被连接啊
Don't let go of your desires.
不要放手……欲望
The future exists only for those who can connect their desires.
只有攥紧欲望的人……才能获得未来
Reo...
玲央
Otter...
水獭
Who are you?
你是谁
I'm Otter.
我是水獭
You were reborn to be my doll.
你已重生为我的人偶
I want to see Reo.
我想见玲央
Sure.
没问题
He wishes to see you again very much.
他也很想见你
But there's just one condition...
但是有个条件……
Once the background blends together, there's an invisible street corner
There we are, crying out with fading voices
Go forth with the tearing pain
As though you'd just crawled away from the worst night ever
You're always alone
Your heart is shouting a sound of desire
If we can ever talk again, if we can ever connect
I'd be overwhelmed
You grow more and more distant
I chase after you
To tell you my brand new feelings for you
I run like mad
Present, past and future
I want to be connected with you
By our feelings, by the depths of our souls
I can't guarantee you'll survive, kero.
我不能保证你们能活下来 呱呱
Are you still going to go take back the dishes, kero?
即使这样你们也要拿回希望之皿吗 呱呱
I've made up my mind.
我决定了
Kazuki...
一稀……
寒天果冻
Keppi!
So this is where you were hiding.
原来你躲在这里啊
Too bad, though.
不过很可惜
The otter barrier won't work on me.
防水獭屏障无法作用于我身上
We're kappas, after all.
毕竟我们是河童
Kappas?
河童？
They were my vassals, kero.
他们是我的家臣 呱呱
Reo, what in the world is—
玲央 你到底要——
All I want is the Dishes of Hope.
我想要的只是希望之皿
Where's the last one?
最后一个在哪里
Look at what you did to Enta!
看看你对燕太做的什么
Give me back the other four!
把那其他四个盘子还给我
Kazuki...
一稀……
Hey, you're the kid I shot.
嘿 你就是被我枪击的那个小孩儿啊
Four more hours.
还有四个多小时
Sucks to be you.
很遗憾
You won't last until morning.
你活不到明天早上
Four more hours?!
四个多小时？
We don't have time.
我们没时间了
Tell me where the dishes are.
告诉我盘子在哪里
So we both need the dishes for something dear to us.
所以我们都需要盘子来达成重要的事情
Four more hours...
还要四个多小时……
Four more hours!
还要四个多小时
I promise I'll save you.
我保证我会救了燕太
Please believe me, Enta.
相信我 燕太
Kazuki!
一稀
That's hilarious.
真是可笑
No one hesitates to give up their connections for the sake of their desires.
人们总是为了欲望而毫不犹豫地放弃联系
Still, I don't want to give up our connection.
即使这样 我也不愿放弃我们之间的联系
For the sake of our future together.
为了我们的未来
How foolish can you be?
你是有多蠢啊
Mabu!
真武
Prince Keppi.
河童王子
Mabu, help me convince Reo, kero.
真武 帮我说服玲央 呱呱
Let's sing that song together, like in the old days.
像以前一样一起歌唱吧
I'm not the man you desire.
我不是你想要的那个人
That's right.
没错
You're a half-baked doll.
你是个半生不熟的人偶
Reo, Otter has found out about the dishes.
玲央 水獭发现了这些希望之皿
He's been reading my memories.
他已经读取了我的记忆
Come on...
你这个人啊……
How many times do you have to disappoint me?
你到底要搞砸我多少次
I'm sick of it, you traitor!
真替你感到恶心 你这个叛徒
Now!
就现在
Reo...
玲央……
I can't take any more of this.
我不能再忍下去了
Reo, you're...
玲央 你……
Don't touch me!
别碰我
You aren't my Mabu.
你不是我的真武
You aren't the Mabu who found me when I was alone.
你不是那个在我独自一人时找到我的真武
You aren't the Mabu who told me the words I wanted to hear!
你不是那个说话我爱听的真武
It hurts.
好疼啊
This is the deepest area, kero.
这是最深的地方了 呱呱
There!
就在那里
Dadadadadadadadadadada...
Darkness!
I've finally found you, Dark Keppi!
我终于找到你了 黑暗Keppi
Dark Keppi?
黑暗Keppi
He's the despair I felt when I was captured by Otter, kero.
他是我被水獭抓到时感受到的绝望 呱呱
During the chaos of war, when I was about to be overtaken by hopelessness,
战乱之中 我被绝望占据
I broke my own Shirikodama into two halves, kero.
尻子玉分裂成了两半 呱呱
Then he's...
那他是……
He's my other half.
他是我的另一半
I came to this world to fuse with Dark Keppi and defeat Otter, kero.
我来到这个世界的使命就是和黑暗Keppi合体并打败水獭 呱呱
Who exactly is this Otter?
水獭到底是什么
Otter...
水獭……
We are your very desires.
我们正是你们的欲望
We have the ability to manifest in this world in the form you most desire.
我们能在这个世界里以你们最想要的外形出现
What have you done to Reo and Mabu, kero?
你对玲央和真武做了什么 呱呱
Otter...
水獭……
I rescued those pitiful kappas.
我救下了那两个可怜的河童
Rescued them?
救了他们？
You seduced them when they were vulnerable, kero.
你在他们脆弱的时候引诱了他们 呱呱
He was already broken.
他已经损坏了
It was an easy task.
这是很容易的事情
Just like this.
就像这样
Otter!
水獭
What the heck?!
怎么回事
Enta!
燕太
We'll be having the Dishes of Hope.
我们会得到希望之皿的
With the despair of never beginning, never ending and never connecting,
和没有开始 没有结束 没有联系的绝望一道
we will take control of this world.
我们将会控制这个世界
Where am I?
我在哪里？
Kazuki...
一稀……
Hey, Enta, can I have the Dishes of Hope?
嘿 燕太 我能拿到希望之皿吗
What?
什么？
Do you like me, Enta?
你喜欢我吗 燕太？
O-Of course I do.
当然了
We're the golden duo.
我们是黄金搭档
Now, go, for my sake.
现在走吧 为了我的愿望
盘子到这儿来
For Kazuki's sake...
为了一稀的愿望……
Enta...
燕太……
This is bad, kero!
非常不妙啊 呱呱
Enta, no!
燕太 不
Thanks, Enta.
谢谢你 燕太
We can have a relationship even more special than being the golden duo.
我们能发展成比黄金搭档还要特别的关系
I want to be connected with Kazuki the same way we always have.
我想和一稀以现在的方式联系在一起
Enta! Are you all right?
燕太 你还好吗
Sorry, I broke the dish.
对不起 我摔碎了盘子
There's no time.
没时间了
Keppi, use my Shirikodama to—
Keppi 使用的我的尻子玉——
That's lame.
你憨啊
Don't try to be cool by sacrificing yourself, idiot.
自我牺牲的方法很差 笨蛋
But...
但是……
I'm not giving up on my future with you, either.
我也不会放弃和你一起的未来
I'm going to haunt you into your next life if you let go before I do.
如果你在我努力之前放弃 那么下辈子我也要纠缠你
You aren't going to forget about me?
你不会就要这样忘记我了吧
We're the golden duo, fool.
我们是黄金搭档 笨蛋
Such obstternance...
真是顽固呢……
Alas, these four dishes will be ours.
但是那四个盘子将会是我们的
That's not happening.
想都别想
Are you otterly sure?
你确定？
What do you think you're doing, Reo?
你在干嘛呢 玲央
Do you not care what happens to Mabu?
你不在意真武身上发生的事情了吗
I don't want that doll!
我不要那种人偶
I'm taking the real Mabu back with these dishes!
我要通过这些盘子带回真正的真武
Otter...
水獭……
Allow me to show this fool the truth.
允许我向这个笨蛋展示真相
Now, Mabu, the time has come to grant your wish.
现在 真武 是时候实现你的愿望了
I thought I'd be happy just being by your side.
和你在一边的话 我就觉得很开心了
If I can't take back your heart, I want to...
如果我不能赢得你的心 那么一切都……
at least satisfy my selfish desires.
至少得满足我自私的愿望
Mabu!
真武
判定 欲望
真武 转换
What?!
什么？
I don't get it.
我搞不清楚
Seriously, what the hell is he thinking?
他到底想要干什么
You need to find out, kero.
需要你去找出 呱呱
If you're prepared for his desire, that is.
你可以通过这种方式来搞清楚他的欲望
Damn it...
可恶
Do it!
来啊
Sing that song!
唱那首歌
真武僵尸
注: 以下歌词翻译来自SweetSub
There's something I have to take back
有那样一件东西 我必须把它挽回
Our connection!
我们的联系
Before the one I like finds out
一定要在我喜欢的那人察觉之前
There's something I have to take back
有那样一件东西 我必须把它挽回
Our connection!
我们的联系
No one can find out...about this secret
千万不能走漏给别人…… 他的秘密啊
Go grab it!
寸珠不让
You and I are supposed
你我原本呀
to be connected
应该可以连接在一起啊
Desires!
欲望
We have to find out the meaning of life
就是为认清 生命的意义啊
Burst!
炸裂迸发
Swim through life and grasp the success
人生中争上游 将光荣握在手
You can believe it's love
要相信那就是 真正的爱
Soul on a dish, stack your plates
皿上之魂 重叠起来
Catch the ball, yank it out
将尻子玉拔掉取出
Grant your wishes, Sarazanmai!
愿望啊实现吧 Sarazanmai
Got it!
来珠不易！
This is... his desire?
这就他的……欲望？
But there's just one condition...
但是有一个条件……
Give up your connection to Reo.
放弃你和玲央之间的联系
Connections are poison.
联系是有毒的
If you speak words of love to Reo,
如果你对玲央表达爱意
your heart will explode, pulverized without leaving so much as a trace behind.
你的心脏将炸得粉碎
Then you'll never be with Reo again.
这样你就永远无法和玲央在一起了
No...
怎么会……
Now, say you hate Reo.
现在 说你讨厌玲央
I want to connect with Reo.
我想和玲央联系在一起
I want to be with Reo.
我想和玲央在一起
I want to connect. I want to be by his side.
我想要联系 想和他在一边
I want to connect.
我想要联系
Reo...
玲央……
I hate Reo.
我讨厌玲央
Good boy, Mabu.
做得不错 真武
Bake me some more ningyoyaki.
给我做一些人形烧吧
For the sake of my future with Reo...
为了我和玲央在一起的未来……
Mabu gave up our connection so he could be with me?
真武为了和我在一起放弃了我们之间的联系
Finally, I've told Reo...
终于 我告诉了玲央
Mabu...
真武……
Mabu!
真武！
You're...
你……
Why?
为什么
Let's go.
我们走吧
We must deliver the Shirikodama to the prince.
我们得要把尻子玉交给河童王子
Hey, wait!
嘿 等等
An emotionless doll who kept betraying me?
无情的人偶一直在背叛我？
A fake?
是假的？
You're...
你真是……
Sara!
Sarazanmai!
Leaking.
泄露中
Mabu!
真武
My wish really came true.
我的愿望终于成真了
I hate Reo.
我讨厌玲央
Good boy, Mabu.
做得好 真武
Bake me some more ningyoyaki.
给我做点人形烧吧
He isn't Mabu if he's giving up his connection with me!
他不是那个放弃和我联系的真武
No!
不
You aren't the Mabu I know!
你不是我认识的真武
Mabu would never look at me like that!
真武不会用这种表情看着我
He's betraying me again, looking all cool.
面无表情的他 今天也依然在辜负着我
He's a doll whose emotions have fallen out of him.
他就是个丢失了感情的 人偶
You would...
你……
never understand!
怎么会理解呢
I was the one who didn't understand.
我才是那个无法理解的人
There's something I want to tell you, Reo.
我有事想跟你说 玲央
Wait, don't say it!
等等 别说出来
My one and only partner, Reo...
我唯一的搭档 玲央
I always have and always will
我一直都会 而且永远都会
love you.
爱你
Desire assimilated.
欲望消化
Mabu...
真武……
I promise I'll connect your desire to the future, kero.
我保证我会让你的欲望联系到未来的 呱呱
真武
没有开始
没有相连
没有终结
真武
Reo...
玲央……
This is another one of Otter's tricks, isn't it?
这不过又是另一个水獭的诡计吧
He's not fooling me!
他不会欺骗我的
The leaks are truth.
泄漏都是真的
You know that, don't you?
你知道的
Keppi!
Keppi
Damn it, Mabu, you broke your promise twice now.
真武那家伙 背叛了两次
You've left me behind.
你把我扔下了
What am I supposed to do now?
我该怎么办
You were the one who said not to let go of desire!
是你说的不要放手欲望
Hand over that dish.
把盘子交出来
No!
不
Reo, that's enough, kero.
玲央 别这样 呱呱
I'm taking him back.
我要把他带回来
I'm not letting anyone stand in my way!
谁都别想妨碍我
Kazuki!
一稀
I'm not giving you the dish.
我不会交出盘子的
I...
我……
I'm not giving up what's precious to me!
我不会放弃对我而言重要的东西
Everyone pisses me off.
所有人都在激怒我
Kazuki!
一稀
Who was I pissed off at?
我又该激怒谁
Who was this burning feeling for?
这股炙热的感情又是为了谁
Who?
谁啊
Who have I forgotten?
我忘了谁？
真武
What?
什么
Reo...
玲央……
真武
I...
我……
My chest hurts.
我胸疼
Toi...
悠……
Enta!
燕太
Are you still alive?
你还活着吗
Barely.
快差不多了
玲央 真武
Reo, Mabu...
玲央 真武……
Get some sleep for now.
安息吧
I had that dream again.
我又做了那个梦
The one where I'm on a giant Nyantaro, and I meet the Little Prince.
我坐在巨型的喵太郎身上 然后我遇到了那个小小的王子
The prince tells me to choose between desire and love.
王子告诉我在欲望和爱之间选择
But I was scared.
但我吓坏了
That if I chose, the big circle might break.
因为如果我选了 那么圆圈就会破碎
This world is facing another trial.
这个世界又在面临另一场审判
Is it connected, or is it not?
是联系上了还是没联系上
You came back, Toi.
你回来了 悠
Thanks for helping Kazu—
谢谢你帮助一稀——
Enta?
燕太？
Enta's death will occur in 40 seconds.
燕太将会在40秒内死掉
Hurry up and make your wish, kero.
快点实现你的愿望 呱呱
Hand over the Dish of Hope.
把希望之皿交出来
Toi?
悠？
My brother is dead.
我哥死了
I'm going to bring him back.
我要把他复活
Enta's death will occur in 15 seconds.
燕太将会在15秒内死亡
Ten, nine, eight,
10 9 8
seven, six, five, four,
7 6 5 4
three, two, one.
3 2 1
想要相连可是却又
没有能力
Stand by me
Please
I don't know if I can become stronger
The rain washes away my tears
I want to be embraced by your warmth
The flickering lightbulb that's been neglected
One morning, it had quietly died
It's almost like you and me
Like the fleeting moment when
we held our hands together
I sat with my arms around my knees
Thinking of the days long gone
Stand by me
Please
I don't know if I can become stronger
Even if you aren't here now
Please give me the courage to reach out
Stand by you
Please
I want to get rid of everything
The rain washes away my tears
I just want to be embraced by your warmth
I'm saved?
我被救了吗
Toi!
悠！
I get it.
我知道了
I would have saved Jinnai if I were you, too.
如果我是你 我也会救阵内
But I'm just so tired.
但我真的厌倦了
Toi...
悠……
Otter!
水獭
Now, cease every connection in this world!
现在 结束这个世上的所有联系吧
绝望 解放
Dadadadadadadadadadada...
Darkness!
Toi!
悠
Let's go outside the circle together...
让我们一起走出圈外吧
And cut off those pointless connections of yours.
然后切断你那没有意义的联系
Toi!
悠！
本故事纯属虚构。
所有登场人物及团体均与现实无关。